Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory02 Mss.B.B61.inventory02
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents B
  - Bowditch, Charles P. (Box 9)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19; 3p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
    - From Boas, 1909 May 19
    - From Boas, 1909 May 24
    - From Boas, 1909 May 29
    - From Boas, 1909 June 1
    - From Boas, 1909 June 22
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25
    - From Boas, 1909 July 10
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 5
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 5
    - From Boas, 1910 May 20
    - From Boas, 1910 June 2
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 14
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 11; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 7; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 13
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 24
    - enc. list of volumes, 1920 Aug. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1900 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Nov. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1903 Jan. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1904 May 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 May 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 30
    - To Boas, 1905 July 18
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 20
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 2
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 1
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar.
    - To Boas, 1906 July 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 20
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 15
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 May 1
    - To Boas, 1907 May 29
    - To Boas, 1907 June 3
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1908 May 13
    - To Boas, 1908 May 22
    - To Boas, 1908 May 25
    - To Boas, 1909 May 17; 5p
    - To Boas, 1909 May 22
    - To Boas, 1909 May 27
    - To Boas, 1909 May 28
    - To Boas, 1909 June 1
    - To Boas, 1909 June 2
    - To Boas, 1909 June 21
    - To Boas, 1909 June 24
    - To Boas, 1909 June 28
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 14
    - To Boas, 1910 May 4
    - To Boas, 1910 May 23
    - To Boas, 1910 June 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Nov. 15
    - To Boas, 1911 July 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 19
    - CPB -- from R. Burkitt, 1906 Feb. 16
    - CPB -- from J.W. Fewkes, 1906 Jan. 10
    - CPB -- from E.L. Hewett, 1906 Jan. 16
  - Bowditch, H.P. (Box 9)
    - 1893 Dec. 9, 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 June 11
      missing: 3/77
    - From Boas, 1908 June 19
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1894 July 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 6
  - Bowditch, I. (Box 9)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1929 Sep. 18; 1p
  - Bower, R. W. (Box 10)
  - Bowerman, Helen Cox (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 23; 2p
  - Bowers, A.U. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 21; 2p
  - Bowers, G.B. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 10; 1p
  - Bowes, James L. (Box 10)
    - From B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 7
  - Bowie, W. Russell (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 11; 2p
  - Bowie, W. Russell (Mrs.) (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 9; 1p
  - Bowker, R.R. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 17; 1p
  - Bowles, F.H. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Bowman, H. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 19
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 1p
  - Bowman, J.G. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 23
    - JGB -- to C.F. Roos, 1931 July 31; 1p
  - Bowsky, M. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1902 May 14; 5p
      - enc. list of furs, 4p
  - Boyd, V. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Boyle, David (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 7
  - Brabant, A.J. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 2
  - Brackett, D.G. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 11; 1p
      enc. receipt
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 29
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 16; 1p
  - Bradley, Lyman R. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 5; 2p
    - (see FB Open Letter 1938 Jan. re Spain), 1937 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p
  - Brady, Mary (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1940 July 1; 1p
  - Brady, M.B. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 7; 1p
  - Brahant & Hesquiet (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 2
  - Brailsford, H.N. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 3; 2p
  - Bramer, J.P. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1926 June 12; 1p
  - Brand, A.R. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 12; 1p
  - Brand, Donald D. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 1p
    - To E. Sapir, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p
  - BRAND, H.L. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 23
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 3
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1917 June 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 June 7
  - Brandeis, L.D. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1935 May 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 June 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Jul 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jun 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jun 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jun 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jul 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jun 16
  - Brandenburg, K. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 26; 1p
  - Brander, W.B. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 23; 1p
  - Brandes, SARAH F. (Mrs.) (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Feb. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 July 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1936 Sep. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 June 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 June 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb. 18and 1935 June 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 18; 1p
    - SFB -- to G, A. Bangs, 1933 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Brandis, Carl (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 13; 1p
      enc. list of journals
  - Brandl, Alvis (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1922 May 27; 2p
  - Brandl, Dr. Rudolf (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1938 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 10; 1p
  - Brandt, K. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 4; 1p
  - Branham, Lucy A. (Box 10)
    - Apr. 1, 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 6; 1p
    - with encs.:, 1932 Jan. 19; 1p
      - Memorandum, 3p
      - cc: Paul Monroe to Eliz. Watson, 11/20/31; 1p
  - Branham, L.G. -- (same as above?) (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 27; 1p
      - enc. list suggested by Lucy Branham and R.C. Thurnwald to L.G. Branham, 1936 Feb. 25
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 28; 1p
  - Branner, John C. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1887 June 9
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 10; 1p
  - Branting, S. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 16; 1p
  - Braschi, Victor M. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 21; 3p
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 30
    - VMB -- from Lejeune Flores & Cia, 1912 Mar. 20; 2p
  - Brauer, Max (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 18; 1p
  - Brauerei, Julius Urbach (Box 10)
    - From Boas, ? Jan. 30; 1p
  - Braun (Box 10)
    - From Marjorie (Mrs. George) McAneny, 1919 Dec. 6; 2p
  - Braun, Oscar (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 8; 3p
  - Braun, Theodore F. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 4; 1p
  - Braun, W.A. (Box 10)
    - To Barnard College, 1923 Apr. 3; 1p
  - Braun, Wilhelm -- (same as above?) (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 23; 1p
    - To Germanistic Soc. of America, 1918 May 7; 1p
  - Brauner, L. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 11; 2p
  - Braus, Hermann (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Breasted, C. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1935 Oct. 25; 1p
  - Breasted, G.H. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p
  - Breasted, J.H. -- (same as above?) (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 16; 1p
    - see FB to R.S. Woodworth, 1931 Sep. 2
  - Breckenfelder, Harry (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 6; 3p
  - Breckinridge, S.P. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 14; 1p
  - Bregsig (?) (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 22
  - Breit, G. (Box 10)
    - From N. Bohr, enc. with GB to L.C. Dunn, 1935 Feb. 17
    - To L.C. Dunn, 1935 Feb. 17
      enc. N. Bohr to GB & A. v. Hippel's C.V.
    - From Szilard, L., 1933 May
  - Breitenfield, S. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1910 June 23
  - Brennan, K.C. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 3; 1p
  - Brennèche, Edward (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1905 Sep. 21; 1p
  - Brennecke, Ernest, Jr. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 2; 1p
  - Brenner, Anita (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 July 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 9 & Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 May 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 18; 7p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 25; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 2; 3p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 6; 1p
  - Brenner, I. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 20; 1p
  - Brenner, J.C. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1913 Sep. 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep. 18
  - Brenstorck, V.M. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sep. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sep. 26; 1p
  - Brenter, C.O. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 5
  - Brentin, W.T. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 23
  - Bresciano, G. (Box 10)
    - To Corrado Gini, 1920 June 30; 2p
  - Breslau, Germany (Box 10)
    - Hauptbücherei der Kgl. Tech. Hochschule
      (See Pescheck)
    - Staats-und Universitäts-Bibliothek
      (See Milkau)
  - Breten, Adolf (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 7
  - Breton, Adele C. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 19
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1914 June 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 18
    - To Boas, 1912 July 13
    - To Boas, 1912 July 17
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 10
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 23
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 12
  - Breuer, Kurt (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 28; 1p
  - Brewster, Dorothy (Box 10)
    - see Ralph Roeter, 1939 May 10
    - co-signed, 1939 July 18; 1p
    - co-signed, 1941 Oct. 18; 2p
      enc. pamphlet
  - Brewster, W.T. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 9; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 4
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 2
  - Breysig, Kurt (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 28; 2p
  - Brickner, S.M. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1899 Sep. 28; 1p
  - Bridge, John (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 4; 1p
    - To E.P. Boas, 1942 Dec. 24; 1p
  - Brieson, Arthur von (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 3; 2p
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 15
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 31
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 5; 4p
    - (form letter by FB co-signed), 1904 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 May 20; 3p
    - To Boas, 1908 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 1
  - Briffault, R. [Robert?] (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 21; 1p
    - (see F. Boas open letter), 1933 Dec.
  - Brigham, G.R. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 2
  - Brigham, Wm. T., 1917 Nov. 10 (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1906 May 1
  - Brightman, Edgar S. (Box 10)
    - (see FB to C.A. Adams), 1942 Mar. 12
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 13
  - Brill, A.A. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 3; 1p
  - Brill, E.J. (& Co.) (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1903 June 9
    - From Boas, 1909 May 10; 2p
    - From Boas, 1909 May 18; 3p
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 31and June 1
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 23; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 July 9; 2p
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 22
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 30
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 June 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 31; bill
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 4; 2p
    - (draft of agreement), 1920 Oct. 4
    - (revision of above), 1920 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1923 Aug. 29; recpt
    - To Boas, 1939 June 17; 1p
    - EJB -- to S. Hagar, 1920 Sep. 4; 1p
    - EJB -- to R.W. Tower, 1920 Aug. 13; 1p
      - (enc. with F.A. Lucas), 1920 Oct. 4
  - Brill, Isidor C. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1927 June 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 June 14; 1p
  - Brillinger, G.S. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 19
  - Bringham, C.S. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 20
  - Bringham, J. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1909 Dec. 18
  - Brink, L.B. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 21; 2p
  - Brinton, Daniel Garrison, 1887 Nov. 21 (Box 10)
    - 1892 Jan. 12
    - From Boas, 1892 Jan. 28
    - From Boas, 1894 Apr. 4
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1898 Dec. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1886 Sep. 1
    - To Boas, 1887 Jan. 2
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1887 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1887 June 9
    - To Boas, 1887 July 23
    - To Boas, 1887 Aug. 27
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 26
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1888 July 27
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1890 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1890 May 6
    - To Boas, 1890 May 30
    - To Boas, 1891 May 14
    - To Boas, 1892 Jan. 12, Jan. 28 & 1892 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1892 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1893 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1893 Apr. 19
    - To Boas, 1893 July 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1893 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 Apr. 4
    - To Boas, 1894 May 26
    - To Boas, 1894 June 22
    - To Boas, 1894 June 24
    - To Boas, 1894 June 28
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1894 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1894 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1895 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1896 May 23
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1896 Sep. 15
    - To Boas, 1896 Oct. 30
    - To Boas, 1896 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1898 Jan. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Feb. 10andFeb. 14
    - To Boas, 1898 June 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 June 13; 3p
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 Oct. 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 30 and Dec. 1/98 and Dec. 2; 1p
    - DGB -- from W.J. McGee, 1898 Sep. 20
  - BAAS (Brit. Assn. for Advancement of Science (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 29
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 23
    - To FB from G. Griffiths, 1898 Nov. 19; 2p
  - British Columbia, Governor of (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 25; 2p
    - To Boas from W.E. Ditchburn, 1930 Dec. 5
      enc. with A.M. Fairbairn
    - To Boas from W.E. Ditchburn, 1930 Dec. 8
  - British Consulate General (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p
  - Brittain, W.H. (Box 10)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 8
      See also Mogill university
  - Brittain, W.M. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 13
    - To Boas, 1909 June 19
    - WMB -- to F.P. Keppel, 1906 Aug. 17
  - Britten, Marri on H. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 25; 1p
  - Britton, N.L. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 22
    - From Boas, 1905 Apr. 29
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1906 May 15
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 28; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 2
    - From Boas, 1908 June 12
    - From Boas, 1909 Nov. 18
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 June 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1915 July 9
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 5; 3p
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 25
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep. 22
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 8
    - From Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1915 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1916 Sep. 29
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 13
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 24
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 16
    - From Boas, 1917 May 1
    - From Boas, 1917 May 8; 7p
    - From Boas, 1917 May 14
    - From Boas, 1917 July 15
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 8
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 14
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 30; 1p
      - enc. draught, 1918 Mar. 30; 3p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Jan. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1908 June 15
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 13
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1915 May 12
    - To Boas, 1915 June 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 26
    - To Boas, 1915 Sep. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1915 Dec. 10
    - To Boas, 1916 May 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 June 6
    - To Boas, 1916 July 19
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 29 and Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep. 29
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 May 19
    - To Boas, 1917 May 21
    - To Boas, 1917 June 28
    - To Boas, 1917 July 20
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 11; 1p
    - see N.Y. Acad. Sci., 1921 Feb. 17
    - minutes of Acad. Sci., 1921 Nov. 22; 2p
    - Enc. minutes of Porto Rico Com., 1921 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 12; 1p
    - NLB -- to F. T. Gates, 1918 Mar. 10; 1p
    - NLB -- to Porto Rico Com. of Agri. & Labor, 1917 Sep. 11
    - NLB -- to G. McAneny, 1918 Mar. 11; 1p
    - NLB -- to N.Y. Acad. Sci. Porto Rico Com., 1925 Jan. 13; 1p
    - NLB -- to A. Yager, 1917 June 28
    - NLB -- from Yager, 1916 Aug. 16
  - Brock, R.W. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 25
    - From Boas, 1910 May 14; 9p
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 May 9
    - From Boas, 1910 May 16
  - Brock, Wallace D. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1937 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 20; 1p
  - Brockett, P. (Box 10)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 May 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Sep 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec 9; 1p
    - PB -- to T.H. Morgan, 1931 Mar 12; 1p
  - Brockhaus, F.A., 1886 Jan. 8 (Box 10)
  - Brode, H.S. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct 24
  - Brodhead, H. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb 28; 1p
  - Brodrick, A.H. (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan 29; 1p
      - see Myres, J.L., 1934 Aug 31
      - see Myres, J.L., 1934 Sep 10
    - AHB -- from Butler, N.M., 1933 Jul 5
    - AHB -- from Butler, N.M., 1933 Jul 21
    - AHB -- to Butler, N.M., 1933 Jul 11
  - Brodsky, W. (Box 11)
    - From Boas, 1935 June 3; 1p
  - Brody, Jack (Box 11)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 31; 1p
  - Brody, Philip M. (Box 11)